A Guide to the Asia Society Exhibition files FA258
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ancient Cambodian Sculpture, Exhibited: 1969 October-December
  - Catalogue: Second Proofs with Corrections, undated (Box 66, Folder 550)
  - Condition Reports, undated (Box 66, Folder 551)
  - Correspondence: General, 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 552)
  - Correspondence: Sherman E. Lee, 1967-1969 (Box 66, Folder 553)
  - Correspondence: With Lenders, 1968-1970 (Box 66, Folder 554)
  - Daily Reports, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 555)
  - Events, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 556)
  - Guest Book, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 557)
  - Installation, 1967, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 558)
  - Installation: Photos and Negatives, undated (Box 67, Folder 559)
  - Insurance, 1968-1970 (Box 67, Folder 560)
  - Lectures, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 561)
  - Loan Agreements, 1968-1971 (Box 67, Folder 562)
  - Opening, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 563)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1969-1972 (Box 67, Folder 564)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 68, Folder 565)
  - Photos: Objects Not in Show, undated (Box 68, Folder 566)
  - Publicity, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 567)
  - Refusals and Withdrawals, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 568)
  - Rubbings, 1959, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 569)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 570)
- "Animal Style" Art from East to West, Exhibited: 1970 January-March
  The Exhibition was a joint effort of The University Museum of the University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, and the Asia House Gallery. Material for the Exhibition was chosen by Mrs. Emma C. Bunker, Research Associate of Oriental Art at the Denver Art Museum, Denver, Colorado, Mr. C. Bruce Chatwin of the University of Edinburgh, and Dr. Ann R. Farkas, Assistant Professor, Department of Art History and Archaeology of Colombia University, New York, New York. Following its display at Asia House, the Exhibition traveled to The University Museum of the University of Pennsylvania and to the M. H. de Young Memorial Museum, San Francisco, California.
  - Acoustiguide Script, undated (Box 68, Folder 571)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 572)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 573)
  - Catalogue: Chatwin Manuscript, undated (Box 68, Folder 574)
  - Catalogue: Corrected Proofs, undated (Box 69, Folder 575)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 69, Folder 576)
  - Catalogue: Galley Proofs with Corrections, undated (Box 69, Folder 577)
  - Catalogue: Galley Proofs with Corrections, undated (Box 69, Folder 578)
  - Catalogue: Galley Proofs with Corrections, undated (Box 70, Folder 579)
  - Catalogue: Galley Proofs with Corrections, undated (Box 70, Folder 580)
  - Catalogue: Galley Proofs with Corrections, undated (Box 70, Folder 581)
  - Catalogue: Introductory Text Retyped, undated (Box 70, Folder 582)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 583)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Typed, undated (Box 70, Folder 584)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript with G. B. Washburn Corrections, undated (Box 71, Folder 585)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, Catalogue Notes, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 586)
  - Catalogue: Text Illustration Correspondence, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 587)
  - Correspondence: Emma C. Bunker, 1966-1970 (Box 71, Folder 588)
  - Correspondence: C. Bruce Chatwin, 1968-1970 (Box 71, Folder 589)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1960-1963 (Box 71, Folder 590)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1964-1965 (Box 72, Folder 591)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1966-1971 (Box 72, Folder 592)
  - Correspondence: Ann R. Farkas, 1968-1969 (Box 72, Folder 593)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1960, 1966-1969 (Box 72, Folder 594)
  - Correspondence: Loans, A-B, 1968-1970 (Box 72, Folder 595)
  - Correspondence: Loans, C-K, 1968-1970 (Box 72, Folder 596)
  - Correspondence: Loans, L-O, 1968-1970 (Box 72, Folder 597)
  - Correspondence: Loans, P-S, 1968-1970 (Box 73, Folder 598)
  - Correspondence: Loans, T-Z, 1968-1970 (Box 73, Folder 599)
  - Daily Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 600)
  - Guest Book, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 601)
  - Installation, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 602)
  - Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 603)
  - Lectures, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 604)
  - Loan Agreements A-G, 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 605)
  - Loan Agreements H-P, 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 606)
  - Loan Agreements R-Z, 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 607)
  - Loan List: Bunker Corrections, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 608)
  - Loan List: Farkas Corrections and Chatwin Corrections (Cable only), 1968 (Box 74, Folder 609)
  - Loan List, Master (Incorporating All Corrections), 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 610)
  - Loan Lists, Original: Bunker, Chatwin, Farkas, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 611)
  - Loan Refusals and Withdrawals, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 612)
  - Opening, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 613)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 614)
  - Packing and Shipping Returns, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 615)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 75, Folder 616)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 75, Folder 617)
  - Publicity, 1965-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 618)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 619)
  - Symposium, 1968-1970 (Box 76, Folder 620)
  - Travel of Exhibition: Philadelphia, 1966-1970 (Box 76, Folder 621)
  - Travel of Exhibition: San Francisco, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 622)
- Masterpieces of Asian Art in American Collections II, Exhibited: 1970 April-June
  The Exhibition, to mark the 10th anniversary of the Asia House Gallery, echoed the first Exhibition held at Asia House in 1960. Items for the Exhibition were chosen with the help of the 15 members of the Gallery's Advisory Committee. The catalogue for the Exhibition was designed and edited by Virginia Field, Assistant Director of the Asia House Gallery.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 623)
  - Acoustiguide Script: Draft, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 624)
  - Catalogue: Annotated File Copy, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 625)
  - Benefit, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 626)
  - Catalogue: Bibliographical References, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 627)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 628)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 629)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence: Photos, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 630)
  - Catalogue: Final Proofs: Photos, undated (Box 77, Folder 631)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript Returned from Printer, undated (Box 77, Folder 632)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, undated (Box 77, Folder 634)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 633)
  - Catalogue: Tenth Anniversary Hardcover Edition, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 635)
  - Catalogue: Xerox Set, undated (Box 77, Folder 636)
  - Citation Style Guide, undated (Box 78, Folder 637)
  - Condition Report Book, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 638)
  - Correspondence A-C, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 639)
  - Correspondence D-E, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 640)
  - Correspondence F-M, 1969-1971 (Box 78, Folder 641)
  - Correspondence N-Q, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 642)
  - Correspondence R-Z, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 643)
  - Correspondence: Gallery Advisory Council, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 644)
  - Correspondence: General, 1969-1971 (Box 78, Folder 645)
  - Daily Reports, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 646)
  - Financial, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 647)
  - Guest Book, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 648)
  - Installation, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 649)
  - Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 650)
  - Loan Forms A-H, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 651)
  - Loan Forms I-Z, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 652)
  - Opening, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 653)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 654)
  - Packing and Shipping for Returns to Lenders, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 655)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 80, Folder 656)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 80, Folder 657)
  - Publicity, 1969-1970 (Box 80, Folder 658)
  - Refusals and Withdrawals, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 659)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 660)
  - Slides for G. B. Washburn Lecture, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 661)
  - Working File, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 662)
- Asian Art: Selections from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Exhibited: 1970 October-December
  The Exhibition of 70 works of art from the private collection of Mr. and Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd was selected and catalogued by Dr. Sherman E. Lee, Director of The Cleveland Museum of Art and its Curator of Oriental Art.
  - Acoustiguide: Draft Notes, undated (Box 81, Folder 663)
  - Acoustiguide Script, undated (Box 81, Folder 664)
  - Catalogue, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 665)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 666)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 667)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 668)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 669)
  - China Institute, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 670)
  - Condition Report, undated (Box 82, Folder 671)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 82, Folder 672)
  - Correspondence: Sherman E. Lee, 1970, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 673)
  - Correspondence: Mr. and Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 674)
  - Daily Reports, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 675)
  - Installation, 1969-1970 (Box 82, Folder 676)
  - Insurance, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 677)
  - Lecture, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 678)
  - Loan Lists, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 679)
  - Opening, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 680)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 681)
  - Publicity, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 682)
  - Publicity: Apollo, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 683)
  - Publicity: Art News, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 684)
- Byōbu: Japanese Screens from New York Collections, Exhibited: 1971 January-March
  The Exhibition of 26 screens was shown in two sections of 13 screens each in the winter of 1971. Section I was shown from January-February and Section II from February-March. Professor Miyeko Murase, Associate Professor of Art History at Columbia University, New York, New York, chose the works to be included and also write the catalogue for the Exhibition.
  - Acoustiguide Script, Section I, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 685)
  - Acoustiguide Script, Section II, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 686)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 687)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 83, Folder 688)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript: Arnold Corrections for Final Version, undated (Box 83, Folder 689)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript: Final Version, Working Set, Corrections for Printer, undated (Box 83, Folder 690)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript: G. B. Washburn Corrections, undated (Box 83, Folder 691)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript: Jackson Burke Corrections, undated (Box 83, Folder 692)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript: Original Uncorrected, undated (Box 83, Folder 693)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript: Virginia Field and Arnold Corrections on First Version, undated (Box 84, Folder 694)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, undated (Box 84, Folder 695)
  - Catalogue: Typed Manuscript, undated (Box 84, Folder 696)
  - Catalogue: Typed Manuscript - Incomplete, undated (Box 84, Folder 697)
  - Ceramic Pots, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 698)
  - Condition Reports, undated (Box 84, Folder 699)
  - Condition Reports II, undated (Box 84, Folder 700)
  - Correspondence: General, 1964-1967, 1970-1972 (Box 84, Folder 701)
  - Correspondence with Lenders, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 702)
  - Correspondence with Specialist (Miyeko Murase), 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 703)
  - Daily Reports, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 704)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 705)
  - Installation, 1967, 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 706)
  - Lectures, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 707)
  - Loan Forms, Section I, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 708)
  - Loan Forms, Section II, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 709)
  - Loan Lists, 1969-1970 (Box 85, Folder 710)
  - Opening, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 711)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 712)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 85, Folder 713)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 85, Folder 714)
  - Publicity, 1970-1972 (Box 85, Folder 715)
  - Slide Permission Letters, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 716)
- Chinese Gold, Silver, and Porcelain from The Kempe Collection, Exhibited: 1971 April-June
  The objects in the Exhibition were selected by Dr. Bo Gyllensvärd, Director of the Museum of Far Eastern Antiquities in Stockholm, Sweden, for circulation by the International Exhibitions Foundation. In addition to its showing at the Asia House Gallery, the Exhibition appeared at several art museums around the United States, including museums in Seattle, Washington, San Francisco, California, Houston and Dallas, Texas, Columbus, Ohio, and Denver, Colorado.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1970-1971 (Box 86, Folder 717)
  - Acoustiguide Script: Draft, undated (Box 86, Folder 718)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1965-1966, 1970-1972 (Box 86, Folder 719)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 86, Folder 720)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, 1970-1971 (Box 86, Folder 721)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 722)
  - Catalogue: Typed Manuscript, undated (Box 87, Folder 723)
  - Catalogue: Typed Manuscript, undated (Box 87, Folder 724)
  - Condition Reports, undated (Box 87, Folder 725)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1970-1971 (Box 87, Folder 726)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1968-1971 (Box 87, Folder 727)
  - Daily Reports, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 728)
  - Damaged Objects, 1971-1972. 1974 (Box 88, Folder 729)
  - Installation, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 730)
  - International Exhibitions Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 88, Folder 731)
  - Lectures, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 732)
  - Loan List, undated (Box 88, Folder 733)
  - Opening, 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 734)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 735)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 88, Folder 736)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 88, Folder 737)
  - Photos: Inferior, undated (Box 89, Folder 738)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 89, Folder 739)
  - Publicity, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 740)
- Ancient Indonesian Art of the Central and Eastern Javanese Periods, Exhibited: 1971 October-November
  The objects in the Exhibition were chosen by Jan Fontein, Curator of Asiatic Art at the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, Massachusetts. The Exhibition marked the first time the Government of Indonesia allowed the nation's treasures to leave the country. Dr. Fontein also authored the catalogue, which was published in both English and Indonesian. The Exhibition was subsequently shown in Kansas City, Missouri, and Los Angeles and San Francisco, California.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 741)
  - Borobudur, 1967-1969 (Box 89, Folder 742)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1969-1972 (Box 89, Folder 743)
  - Correspondence: American Embassy, Djakarta, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 744)
  - Correspondence: American Overseas Petroleum, 1966-1972 (Box 89, Folder 745)
  - Correspondence: Caltex Pacific Indonesia, 1966-1968, 1970-1972 (Box 89, Folder 746)
  - Correspondence: Jan Fontein, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 747)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1969-1973 (Box 89, Folder 748)
  - Correspondence: Datus C. Smith Jr.: Finance, 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 749)
  - Catalogue: "Kesenian Indonesia Purba", 1971 (Box 90, Folder 750)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript Sent to Printer, undated (Box 90, Folder 751)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1970-1971 (Box 90, Folder 752)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, undated (Box 90, Folder 753)
  - Catalogue: Typed Manuscript, undated (Box 91, Folder 754)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: General, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 91, Folder 755)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Kansas City, 1970-1972 (Box 91, Folder 756)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Los Angeles, 1970-1972 (Box 91, Folder 757)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: San Francisco, 1967, 1971-1972 (Box 91, Folder 758)
  - Correspondence: American Embassy, Djakarta, 1966-1972 (Box 91, Folder 759)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box 91, Folder 760)
  - Correspondence: Jan Fontein, 1966-1971 (Box 91, Folder 761)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Ide Anak Agung Gde Agung, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 762)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Indrosoegondho, 1966-1968 (Box 91, Folder 763)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Soejono Kromodimoeljo, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 764)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Adam Malik, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 765)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Ida Bagus Mantra, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 766)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Mashuri, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 767)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Soekmono, 1965-1971 (Box 92, Folder 768)
  - Correspondence: Foreign: Moh. Amir Sutaarga, 1966-1972 (Box 92, Folder 769)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, Miscellaneous, 1966-1972 (Box 92, Folder 770)
  - Correspondence: Inactive, 1962-1963, 1966-1969 (Box 92, Folder 771)
  - Correspondence: Indonesian Consulate, New York, 1966-1968, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 772)
  - Correspondence: Indonesian Embassy, Washington, D.C., 1967-1971 (Box 92, Folder 773)
  - Correspondence: J. E. van Lohuizen-de Leeuw, 1964-1966 (Box 92, Folder 774)
  - Curators' Visit, 1970-1972 (Box 92, Folder 775)
  - Daily Reports, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 776)
  - Damages, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 777)
  - Financial: JDR 3rd Fund, 1965-1971 (Box 92, Folder 778)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 92, Folder 779)
  - Installation, 1971-1972 (Box 93, Folder 780)
  - Installation: Extra Photos, undated (Box 93, Folder 781)
  - Lectures, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 782)
  - Lists, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 783)
  - Loan Agreements, Insurance, 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 784)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968-1970, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 785)
  - Monuments: Photos Not Used, undated (Box 93, Folder 786)
  - Opening, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 787)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1970-1972 (Box 94, Folder 788)
  - Packing Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 94, Folder 789)
  - Photographs, 1967, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 790)
  - Photos: Indonesian Photos from Pan Am, undated (Box 94, Folder 791)
  - Photos: Indonesian Photos from Pan Am, undated (Box 95, Folder 792)
  - Photos: Indonesian Photos from Pan Am, undated (Box 95, Folder 793)
  - Photos: Inferior (1-10), undated (Box 95, Folder 794)
  - Photos: Inferior (11-20), undated (Box 95, Folder 795)
  - Photos: Inferior (31-40), undated (Box 96, Folder 797)
  - Photos: Inferior (21-30), undated (Box 96, Folder 796)
  - Photos: Inferior (41-50), undated (Box 96, Folder 798)
  - Photos: Inferior (51-60), undated (Box 96, Folder 799)
  - Photos: Inferior (61-70), undated (Box 96, Folder 800)
  - Photos: Inferior (71-80), undated (Box 96, Folder 801)
  - Photos: Inferior (81-90), undated (Box 97, Folder 802)
  - Photos: Inferior (91-100), undated (Box 97, Folder 803)
  - Photos: Inferior (100-111), undated (Box 97, Folder 804)
  - Progress Reports and Memos, 1966-1971 (Box 97, Folder 805)
  - Publicity, 1968, 1971-1974 (Box 97, Folder 806)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 807)
  - Washburn Trip and Notes, 1966-1967 (Box 98, Folder 808)
- Scholar Painters of Japan: The Nanga School, Exhibited: 1972 January-February
  The objects in the Exhibition were chosen by James Cahill, Professor of the History of Art at the University of California, Berkeley, and Curator of Oriental Art at the University Museum. The Exhibition was shown in two sections of approximately 35 paintings each: Section I, January 13-February 6, and Section II, February 9-27. Professor Cahill authored the catalogue for the Exhibition. Following its showing at Asia House, the Exhibition traveled to the University Museum in Berkeley, California.
  - Acoustiguide Script, Section I, 1971-1972 (Box 98, Folder 809)
  - Acoustiguide Script, Section II, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 810)
  - Catalogue: Corrected Copy from Which New Pages Were Typed, undated (Box 98, Folder 811)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 98, Folder 812)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 813)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, undated (Box 99, Folder 814)
  - Catalogue: Typed Manuscript, undated (Box 99, Folder 815)
  - Catalogue: Version Sent to Printers, undated (Box 99, Folder 816)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Berkeley, 1969-1972 (Box 99, Folder 817)
  - Condition Reports Book, 1971-1972 (Box 99, Folder 818)
  - Correspondence: Kenji Adachi, 1970-1972 (Box 99, Folder 819)
  - Correspondence: Mr. and Mrs. Jackson Burke, 1968-1973 (Box 99, Folder 820)
  - Correspondence: James Cahill, 1967-1972 (Box 100, Folder 821)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1970-1972 (Box 100, Folder 822)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1968-1972 (Box 100, Folder 823)
  - Correspondence: Susumu Suzuku, 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 824)
  - Correspondence with Lenders, 1969-1970 (Box 100, Folder 825)
  - Curators, 1971-1972 (Box 100, Folder 826)
  - Daily Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 100, Folder 827)
  - Damage in Berkeley, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 828)
  - Financial, 1967-1972 (Box 100, Folder 829)
  - Installation, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 830)
  - Insurance, 1971-1972 (Box 101, Folder 831)
  - Lectures, 1971-1972 (Box 101, Folder 832)
  - Loan Agreement, 1970-1972 (Box 101, Folder 833)
  - Loan Lists, 1969-1971 (Box 101, Folder 834)
  - Opening, 1971-1972 (Box 101, Folder 835)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1971-1972 (Box 101, Folder 836)
  - Photos, undated (Box 101, Folder 837)
  - Photos: Deleted, 2-32, undated (Box 101, Folder 838)
  - Photos: Deleted, 33-57, undated (Box 101, Folder 839)
  - Photos: Deleted: Oversize, undated (Box 101, Folder 840)
  - Photos: Deleted Sets (7, 9, 11, 14), undated (Box 102, Folder 841)
  - Photos: Deleted Sets (19, 20, 24, 25), undated (Box 102, Folder 842)
  - Photos: Deleted Sets (35, 39, 46), undated (Box 102, Folder 843)
  - Photos: Deleted Sets (53, 55), undated (Box 103, Folder 844)
  - Photos: Negatives, undated (Box 103, Folder 845)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 103, Folder 846)
  - Publicity, 1971-1972 (Box 103, Folder 847)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 103, Folder 848)
  - Slides, 1971-1972 (Box 103, Folder 849)
  - Washburn Trip to Asia, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 850)
  - Photos: Deleted: Oversize, undated (Box 126, Folder 1087)
- From the Bosporus to Samarkand: Flat Woven Rugs, Exhibited: 1972 April-June
  The Exhibition opened in May 1969 at The Textile Museum in Washington, D.C., after which it was circulated by the Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service. Its final showing was at the Asia House Gallery in the spring of 1972. The catalogue for the Exhibition was written by Anthony N. Landreau and W. R. Pickering and published by The Textile Museum, Washington, D.C.
  - Acoustiguide Script, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 867)
  - Catalogue: Annotated, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 868)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 869)
  - Condition Reports, undated (Box 105, Folder 870)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 871)
  - Correspondence: Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service, 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 872)
  - Daily Reports, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 873)
  - Installation, 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 874)
  - Lectures, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 875)
  - Opening, 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 876)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 877)
  - Photos, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 878)
  - Publicity, 1969, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 879)
  - Yurts, undated (Box 106, Folder 880)
- Sculptural Jades of China
  The Exhibition, originally scheduled to take place in the spring of 1970 (April-June), was twice postponed (to 1971 April-June and 1972 April-June) and was then postponed indefinitely. Objects for the Exhibition were being selected by Dr. William B. Trousdale, Associate Curator, Department of Anthropology, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C.
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 851)
  - Correspondence: General, 1963-1964, 1967, 1969-1972 (Box 103, Folder 852)
  - Correspondence A-F, 1969-1971 (Box 103, Folder 853)
  - Correspondence G-Z, 1963, 1967-1972 (Box 103, Folder 854)
  - Correspondence: William B. Trousdale, 1965-1972 (Box 104, Folder 855)